[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "South Carolina is the state whose shape most closely resembles a triangle.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Who does Lt. Cmdr. Matt T. Sherman marry in Operation Petticoat?", "correct_answer": "Lt. Dolores Crandall, RN", "incorrect_answers": ["Maj. Edna Heywood, RN", "Lt. Reid, RN", "Lt. Barbara Duran, RN"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the movie Joe Dirt, where did Joe Dirt lose his parents?", "correct_answer": "Grand Canyon", "incorrect_answers": ["Yellowstone National Park", "Mount Rushmore", "Sea World"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The Meryas were a probably Finno-Ugric tribe who lived in the region of modern Russia. This is the first historian to mention them.", "correct_answer": "Jordanes", "incorrect_answers": ["Eusebius of Caesarea", "Priscus", "Sima Guang"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "For what medical condition is non-metallic gold beneficial, according to some studies?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Tuberculosis", "Rheumatoid arthritis", "Inflammation"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The tradition of placing the wedding ring on the third finger of the left hand originates from ancient Egypt, where they believed that a vein in this finger ran directly to the heart.", "correct_answer": "True", "incorrect_answers": ["False"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What color is Arterial Blood?", "correct_answer": "Bright Red", "incorrect_answers": ["Purple", "Reddish Purple", "Dark Red"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which character from the movie American Pie joins the choir in hopes of meeting a girl?", "correct_answer": "Oz", "incorrect_answers": ["Jim", "Kevin", "Finch"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "All of these countries and commonwealth territories have a high divorce rate except one.", "correct_answer": "Sri Lanka", "incorrect_answers": ["Puerto Rico", "Russia", "Qatar"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What Animal House actor went on to co-star in numerous movies, including \u201cWildcats,\u201d The Insider,\u201d and My Cousin Vinny?", "correct_answer": "Bruce McGill", "incorrect_answers": ["Donald Sutherland", "John Belushi", "Tim Matheson"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Did Rosie, the protagonist of Princess Protection Program, leave her home country because someone attempted to assassinate her?", "correct_answer": "Yes", "incorrect_answers": ["No"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What fictional teacher, portrayed by Robin Williams, told his students that, if they felt daring, they could call him O Captain! My Captain!?", "correct_answer": "John Keating", "incorrect_answers": ["Mark Thackeray", "George Feeny", "Jaime Escalante"]}]